前情提要
Previously on Lost
听得见吗?
Can you hear me?
是的  我能听到
Yes! yes, I can hear you.
-你在船上吗?      -什么船?
Hey, are you on a boat? what--what boat?
-你的船  -我不在船上
Your boat. I'm not on a boat.
Naomi  那个跳伞的
Uh, na-Naomi, the parachutist.
谁又是Naomi?
Who? who's Naomi?
有反应了!
I've got it. I've got a signal! it's gonna work.
一定能行的  我们终于要离开这座岛了
It's happening. we're gonna get off of this island.
Desmond在吗?
Is Desmond there?
Penny!
不!
No!
打通那个电话将是末日的开始
Making that call is the beginning of the end.
-你是谁?  -你又是谁?
Who is this? who is this?
我是815航班的幸存者之一
I'm one of the survivors of oceanic flight 815.
你能确定我们的方位吗?
Can you get a fix on our location?
稍等  我们马上赶到
Sit tight. we'll be right there.
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：阿武 思思 newlbs 手术 麦田 天龙 小龙人
校对：许愿 时间轴：灵溪 战痘痘 后期：梁良
这场高速追击...
It's almost 30 minutes now
已经持续了大约半小时
Since the start of this high-speed chase.
目前我们仍无法确认...
We still have no information
驾车者身份
About who's driving this vehicle.
Jeff  请问追击是从哪里开始的?
Jeff, can you tell us where the chase started?
Ruth  据称追击是从...
Ruth, we're hearing reports that the pursuit began
拉布雷亚附近开始的
Near the La Brea Area,
之后穿过10号高速路...
Then traveled through a warehousing district
-以南的一个仓库区  -能看到车上有几人吗?
South of the 10 freeway. can you see how many people are in the car?
看来只有司机一人
It appears to be just the one-- the driver.
但不能确定是否是他本人的车
We're not sure if that's the owner of the car.
你所看到的这些...
What you're seeing here
是城区以南10号公路附近的画面
Are pictures of the 10 freeway south of downtown.
Jeff  那是一辆卡玛洛吗?
Is that a Camaro, Jeff?
对  看起来是辆Vintage  70年初的车型
Yes, it looks like a vintage, early '70s model.
老天
Damn it.
手放在我能看见的地方!
Show us your hands!
摇下车窗  把手伸出来!
Roll down the window and show us your hands now!
左手慢慢打开车门
Now slowly open the door with your left hand.
快从车里出来!
Get out of the car!
慢慢地转过身来!
Turn around... slow!
给我趴下!
On the ground!
快!
Now!
住手
Stop!
你知道我是谁吗!  放手!
Don't you know who I am?! stop! wait!
知道我是谁吗!  我是大洋航班6人之一啊!
Don't you know who I am?! I'm one of the oceanic six!
大洋航班6人之一!
I'm one of the oceanic six!
所以在10辆警车满城追击你的前5分钟...
So five mimutes before you let ten cruiser on a chase across the city
在5分钟前你却在杂货店里东搞西搞
you're minding your own business In a convenience store,
你在杂货店里...直到有东西吓到了你
Until you see something and freak out.
Reyes先生  你为何要逃跑?
Mr. Reyes, why'd you run like that?
你看到了谁?
Who'd you see in there?
听着  哥们儿  我知道你在店里看到了某人
Listen, buddy, I know you saw somebody in that store
-是他吓得你落荒而逃跑上高速路  -我没想...
That made you run away and go on a high-speed-- I wasn't running away
逃谁
from anyone.
你以为我会在乎你是名人吗
If you think I care that you're a celebrity,
你的卡玛洛误闯进了别人家里
You crashed your Camaro in the wrong neighborhood.
我才不是啥名人
I'm not a celebrity.
你不是就凭这个大嚷大叫的吗
Is that why you kept shouting,
"我是大洋航班6人之一啊"
"hey, I'm one of the oceanic six"?
想听听有意思的巧合吗
You wanna know a funny coincidence?
行啊
Sure.
我认识你航班上的人
I knew somebody on your plane.
真的吗
Really?
她叫Ana Lucia Cortez
Her name was Ana Lucia Cortez.
在我晋升探长之前她是我的搭档
She was my partner before I made detective--
黑发...
Dark hair...
美极了
Gorgeous.
也许你认识她
Maybe you knew her.
也许在飞机上见过她
Maybe you met her on the plane...
起飞前见过吗?
Before it took off?
抱歉  我没见过她
Sorry. never met her.
你还是看看录影带吧
Why don't you watch the tape?
也许能给你点启发
Maybe it'll spark something.
我去拿点炸面圈
I'm gonna get a doughnut.
要吃吗
You want one?
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
等我回来  你要告诉我你在躲谁
And when I come back, you're gonna tell me who you ran from.
救命
Help!
救命  让我出去!
Help! let me out!
你到底发什么神经!
What the hell is wrong with you?
你在做什么  Reyes
What are you doing, Reyes?
你想进疯人院吗
Huh? you trying to get tossed into the nuthouse?
如果那是你想要的话
Because if that's what you want,
-伙计 我马上就能把你送进去  -是吗?
I can make that happen right now, my friend. you can?
那太谢谢你了!
Oh, thank you!
实在太感谢了!
Thank you. thank you.
Jack?  你在那吗  伙计
Jack? you there, dude?
海滩呼叫Jack
Beach to Jack.
我在  Hurley  什么事?
Right here, Hurley. what's up?
你们是不是已经到无线电塔了?
Hey, uh, did you guys make it to that radio tower thingy yet?
是的  而且我已经和船上的人联系过了
Yeah, and I talked to the people on the boat.
-他们正赶来接我们  -真的吗  成功了?
They're on their way to pick us up right now. seriously? it worked?
当然  我们这就回海滩
Seriously. we're all on the way back to the beach right now,
所以你开始收拾行李吧  伙计
So you better pack your bags, buddy.
伙计  太棒了
Dude, that's great!
找到他了吗?
Any luck?
没有  没有他的踪影
Nothing. no sign of him.
他不见了
It's like he just disappeared.
-为什么Locke要杀她  他都没见过她  -因为他疯了
Why would Locke kill her? he hadn't even met her-- because he's crazy.
如果他回来了呢?
So what if he comes back?
如果他回来  我就宰了他!
If he comes back, I'm gonna kill him.
我去把大家都叫上
I'm gonna get everybody together.
我们越快回海滩越好
The sooner we get back to the beach, the better.
我们真的就快回家了吗?
Are we really going home?
是的  我们要回家了
Yeah, we're really going home.
真不敢相信  我会在医院里...
I can't believe I'm actually going to have my baby
生下我的孩子
In a hospital.
-得意什么嘛  -我不是那个意思
Oh, rub it in, why don't you? oh, no.
-你们需要帮忙吗  -不用了  我们自己收拾
You ladies need a hand? no, we're just wrapping things up, thanks.
你一定为Bernard感到自豪
You know, you must be very proud of Bernard.
我听说他是个真英雄
I hear he's quite the hero.
这里的所有人都知道
Look, everyone up here knows
真正的英雄是你的男人Claire
That the real hero is your man, claire.
如果不是Charlie关掉了屏蔽信号
If Charlie didn't turn off that gizmo, we'd still be
我们的信号一定还会被干扰
Getting a busy signal on that fancy phone.
所以等他回来了
So you better make sure you treat him real good
你一定要好好伺候他
When we get back.
Rose!
好的  谢谢  不用了
Okay, thanks. I have enough.
我要你帮我一个忙
I need you to do me a favor.
我要你带着Alex
I need you to take Alex
离开这里  越远越好
And get as far from here as possible.
-什么?  -听我说  没时间争论了
What? listen to me. we don't have time for this.
呆在这里的人都会死
Everyone who stays here is going to die.
现在赶快带着Alex离开这里
Now get Alex and get away right now.
我不管你要去哪里  走就行
I don't care where you go. just go.
我不会让我的女儿...
I will not have my daughter--
她才不是你的女儿
She's not your daughter.
我告诉过你我中奖的事吗
Did I ever tell you I won the lottery?
我身价有一亿五千万多
I got, like, $150 million.
一辈子遇到过的最倒霉的事
Worst thing that ever happened to me.
是啊  谁用的着那一亿五千万?
Oh, yeah, who needs $150 million, right?
现现在都没有了  他们一定以为我死了
Now it'll all be gone, cause they all think I'm dead.
等我们获救后...
When we get rescued,
当我回家后...
And I go back...
我就自由了
I'm gonna be free.
我想来个"深水炸弹"
I wanna do a cannonball.
每天都在海滩上走来走去
I've been walking up and down this beach every day
看着这片海
And looking out at this water,
真的想跳下去
And I wanna do a cannonball.
Hurley...
你想跳"深水炸弹"
You wanna do a cannonball,
你就炸吧
Cannonball.
你还好吗  Desmond?
Are you all right, Desmond?
我们得找到Jack
We need to get to Jack.
不能让他联系那艘船
We can't let him get in touch with that boat.
-放松老苏一切就绪  船在路上了  -什么?  不行
Easy, Scotty. everything's cool. boat's on the way. what? on the way? no.
-Charlie在哪?  -不  那个Naomi  她撒谎了
Hey, where's Charlie? no, that woman--Naomi-- she lied.
-船上的人不是他们所说的  -什么?
Look, the people on the boat aren't who they say they are! what?
-那他们是谁?  -Desmond  Charlie在哪?
Then who are they? Desmond, where's Charlie?
-Desmond...  -我不知道  但是我们得马上找到Jack
Desmond-- I don't know, but we need to get in touch with Jack now!
别担心  我们能用对讲机联系到他
It's all right. we can call him. we have a walkie. it's okay. well,
在哪  快拿出来
where is it? get it.
-你说那群人不是他们所说的是什么意思?   -Charlie在哪
What do you mean the people aren't who they say-- where's Charlie?!
抱歉兄弟  我...
I'm--i'm--i'm sorry, brother. i...
是我们的船吗
You think that's our ride?
你好?
Hello?
Jack  我是George Minkowsk
Hey, Jack. this is George Minkowski.
我们正试着确定你们的方位
We're trying to get a lock on your signal there,
但有些射频干扰
But we're getting some rf interference.
我们需要在你的卫星电话上...
We're gonna need to rejigger some of the settings
改下设置
On your sat-phone.
好的  告诉我怎么做
Uh, sure. okay. just tell me what I gotta do.
你让Naomi接吧？
How about you put Naomi on?
Naomi去找柴火了
Naomi went to get some firewood.
你先等一下  我看下能否...
Can you hold on for a second? let me see if I can...
她人呢?
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们要叫医生
Look, we gotta call the doc.
你听见Desmond说的了吗?  Charlie在他的手上写着...
Did you listen to Desmond? Charlie wrote on his hand--
我很遗憾他死了  但我甚至不知道
Look, I'm sorry he's dead, but I don't even know
-"不是Penny的船"什么意思  -找Jack也无济于事
What the hell "not Penny's boat" means. calling Jack accomplishes nothing.
至少能警告他
It would accomplish warning him.
也让货船上的人认识到我们...
it also means warning the people on the freighter
对他们的怀疑  我很确信..
That we're suspicious of them. I have no doubt they're
-在监控我们的联系  如果我们打电话给Jack  -你知道吗？
Monitoring our communications. if we call Jack-- you know what?
对讲机在我手里  我这就打过去
I got the walkie. I'm making the call.
我们最好现在就起程
We better get goin'.
去哪？！
Going where?!
我找到了那女孩的血迹  估计已经跑远了
I found blood--the girl's trail. probably crawled away.
大约快我们10分钟左右
Can't be more than ten minutes ahead of us.
-我们现在就要去找她  -把他一起带上
We should go now and find her. we're taking him with us.
为什么？
And why would we do that?
我不放心他跟任何人在一起  除了我
Because I don't trust him with anybody but me.
大家听好了
All right, listen up.
我要大家回到海滩去
I need all of you to head back down to the beach,
因为等他们到了这里  我们得...
And when these people show up, we wanna make sure
让他们立刻就找到我们
That we're real easy for them to find, okay?
你看起来有些担心啊  Jack
You look worried, Jack.
我唯一担心的是...
The only thing I'm worried about
错过回家的船
Is missing our ride home.
我找到她留下的踪迹了  她朝岛西边去了
I found her trail. she's headed west across the island.
Rousseau已经发现了  我们这就去找她
Rousseau already found it. we're going after her right now.
你确定是她的？
What? are you sure it's hers?
除非有其他人在流血
Unless someone else is bleeding.
但如果她不想我们找到她
Okay, but if she didn't want us to find her,
那她有可能留下假踪迹
Then she could've created a dummy trail.
-我觉得我们该分头行动  -Kate  现在起6小时后
I think we should follow both just in c-- Kate, six hours from now,
我们会坐在船上
We're gonna be sitting
嘲笑咱们这最后一件...
Laughing about the fact that there was one final thing
有分歧的事
That we couldn't agree upon.
Naomi受伤了  她跑进了丛林
Naomi is hurt. she ran into the jungle.
她不会花心思留下假痕迹
She's not thinking about leaving fake trails.
你是对的
You're right.
我会顺着痕迹找到她
I'll track her down.
-你何不带大家回到海滩？  -好的
Why don't you get everybody back to the beach? you got it.
小心  好吗？
Be careful, okay?
你怎么了  Hugo?
What the hell's gotten into you, Hugo?
他们早上都会回来  如果我们等着
They'll all be back in the morning. if we just wait--
-你不会不顾警告等着吧...  -警告
You don't wait with warnings. you... warn.
还以为能作个好梦
Here I was thinking I was gonna get a good night's sleep.
那次你就快赢我了
You almost got me that time.
十局七胜怎么样?
How about best out of seven?
准备好吃药了吗  Hugo?
Are you ready for your meds, Hugo?
顺便说一下
Oh, by the way,
有人来看你了
You have a visitor.
Reyes先生
Mr. Reyes.
你好  我叫Matthew Abbadon
Hello. my name is Matthew Abbadon.
我是大洋航空公司的代理人
I'm an attorney for oceanic airlines.
我们可以谈谈吗？
Can we talk for a few minutes?
好的
Okay.
我来...  Reyes先生
I'm here, mr. Reyes,
因为我们听说了你最近的...插曲
Because we've heard about your recent... episode.
你的被捕  你在这儿的监禁
Your arrest, your incarceration here--
坦白说  我们很难过
Frankly, we feel terrible about it.
因此代表大洋航空公司
So on behalf of oceanic,
我想给你一个邀请
I'd like to extend you an invitation
为了一点改善
For a little upgrade.
哪种...改善？
What... kind of upgrade?
去一个更整洁干净的地方
To a facility where the paint isn't peeling off the walls,
有自己的浴室
Where you'd have your own bathroom.
-你可以看见大海  -我不想看见大海
You can see the ocean from-- I don't wanna see the ocean.
这没问题
No problem.
确实很感谢
Actually, thanks.
我...我在这很好
I'm... I'm fine right here.
你好吗  Reyes先生？
Are you fine, mr. Reyes?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你现在精神病院
You're in a mental institution.
能再说一遍你的身份吗?
Who'd you say you were again?
你有名片吗
I'd like to see a business card.
可能忘在家里了
I must have left them at home.
那我们到此为止了  伙计
Then we're done, dude.
他们还活着吗?
Are they still alive?
什么?
What?
不要明知故问
You heard me.
护士  护士  赶他走!
Nurse! nurse! get out of here!
赶他走  救命  救命
You better get outta here! help me! help me!
-那个人在跟踪我  我没事  救命  -没事了
No, no, no, no. that guy's after me! help me! okay, okay.
没事吧  Hugo?
You all right there, Hugo?
我没事  伙计
Yeah, dude, I'm fine.
想聊聊吗?
You wanna talk about it?
聊什么?
Talk about what?
Charlie
Charlie.
我觉得...
I mean...
你俩是好兄弟  我想...
You two were buddies. I just thought...
不聊天我们才跟得上Jack
We'll probably get to Jack faster if we don't talk.
我上去叫带队的走慢点
I'm gonna head up and tell them to slow down a little.
我跟得上
I can keep up.
好吧
All right, ese.
要帮忙尽管嚷嚷
Just... holler if you need me.
伙计们?
Guys?
伙计们
Guys!
人呢
你们在哪儿
Guys!
伙计们
血迹在这里消失了
The blood trail ends here.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
没有了
It ends.
你意思是她到这里就止住血了?
What, are you telling me that she stopped bleeding here?
不  她耍了我们  她到这后就按原路返回了
No, I'm telling you that she fooled us and doubled back.
赶紧和船上的人说
Better call the boat,
她扎了个好大好大的火把
Tell 'em she's getting a really big bundle of firewood.
电话在哪?
Where is it?
好吧  她偷了你的电话时
Okay, I probably should have told you
我本想告诉你  但鉴于你痛打了我一顿  Jack
That I saw her take the phone, but you beat me up, Jack.
-我欠你的  -你在说什么呢?
I owed you one. what are you talking about?
你们拥抱时  Kate趁机偷走了电话
Kate took it when she hugged you.
她追踪的痕迹是对的  可你不听她的
She found the right trail, too, but you wouldn't listen to her,
我想她也是自找麻烦
So I guess she's taken matters into her own hands.
不过凡事要往好的方面想
But look on the bright side. at least
至少有人知道该做什么
Somebody around here knows what the hell they're doing.
喂?
Hello?
你是谁?
Who's this?
我是Kate
Uh, this is Kate.
你和Jack在一起?
You with Jack?
-不  他不在这  -Naomi在哪里?
No, no, he's not here. where's Naomi?
我们正在找她
Uh, we're looking for her.
什么意思  你们在找她?
What do you mean, you're looking for her?
给我电话
Give me the phone.
Naomi  你受伤了  让我来帮你
Naomi, listen to me. you're hurt. let me help you.
帮我?  过去的三天
Help me? I just spent the last three days
我一直在努力使你们获救
Trying to get you people rescued,
可你们却恩将仇报
And you throw this knife in my back.
不是我们干的
No, that was not us.
-他叫John Locke  -什么?
His name is John Locke. what?
他说你隐瞒了自己的身份
He said that you weren't who you said you were.
我发誓我们不想伤害你  你了解我们的
I swear to god we would never hurt you. you know us.
我们需要你的帮助  求你了
Please, we need your help. please help us.
把电话给我
Give me the phone.
George  我是Naomi
George, it's Naomi.
Naomi  你去哪了?
Naomi, where have you been?
发生什么了?
What's going on over there?
出了点意外
I had an accident.
我受伤了
I'm hurt.
意外?  什么意外?
What? a-an accident? what--what--what accident?
发生什么了?
What happened?
Naomi!
喂?
Hello?
当我跳伞降落时
I hit a tree branch
我被树杈弄伤了
When I parachuted in.
树枝穿破了我的肚子
Took it through my gut.
他们怎么说你去找柴火了?
Why did they tell me you were getting firewood?
我猜他们是不敢告诉你我出事了
I guess they were afraid to tell you what happened to me
直到我亲自跟你说吧  我们收不到信号了
Till I could talk to you myself. we've lost our signal,
我们就找不到你
and we can't come get you.
你能调下你的追踪频率吗?
Can you change your tracking frequency?
好的
Yeah.
现在试试看
Try it now.
很清楚  坚持住  Naomi
Clear as a bell. hang on, Naomi.
我们将尽快带你回来  好吗?
We'll--we'll get you back here asap, okay?
对不起  George
I'm sorry, George.
告诉我妹妹  我爱她
Just tell my sister that I love her.
有人吗?
Hello?
救命
Help!
这儿什么都没有
There's nothing here.
这儿什么都没有  这儿什么都没有
There's nothing here. there's nothing here.
这儿什么都没有
There's nothing here.
你好  Hugo
Hello, Hugo.
你迷路了  Hugo
You got yourself good and lost out here, Hugo.
你是怎么跟队伍走散的?
How did you get separated from the group?
我...
I just...
我猜被落在后面
Fell behind, I guess.
因为这个你就高呼救命?
Is that why you were shouting for help?
是的  我吓了一跳
Well, I got scared.
Desmond说那个站发生什么...
What Desmond said happened down in that station--
不是Penny的船...
"not Penny's boat"...
你确信那是Charlie写在手上的吗?
Are you sure that's what Charlie wrote on his hand?
Jack本来不该叫那些人的
Jack should never have called those people.
我再同意不过
I couldn't agree more.
说服他不要...
It's gonna be hard to...
让这些人来...
Talk him into thinking they're not coming here
会很难的
To rescue us.
是啊  我们已经尽了最大的努力  Hugo
Well, we're just gonna have to try our best, Hugo,
因为如果我们
Because if we
不能说服他放弃那个想法...
Can't talk him out of it...
Charlie就死得毫无价值
Then Charlie died for nothing.
你到底去哪儿啦  Hugo?
Where the hell you been, Hugo?
抱歉  我只是  迷路了
Sorry. I was just, uh, I got lost.
你来这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我来这里的目的跟你一样...警告Jack
I came here for the same reason you did--to warn Jack
关于在船上的那些人
About the people on that boat.
我已经试过一次了
I already gave it a shot,
但我认为一些支持可以增加点儿运气
But I figured I might have better luck with some support.
你想得到我的支持?
You want my support?
告诉我你为什么毁了潜水艇
You can tell me why you destroyed that submarine.
Jin-Soo Kwon
看我好好的
Still in one piece.
兰博
Rambo. ow.
我去跟她说
I'll tell her.
他死了
He's dead.
Charlie... 死了
Charlie's... dead.
不
No.
我要是你  我会小心的
I'd watch out if I were you.
你说什么呢  伙计?
What are you talking about, dude?
那儿有个人  他一直看着你
There's a guy over there. he's staring at you.
-哪个人?  -那个人
What guy? that guy.
嘿  哥们儿
Hey, man.
别跑
Don't run.
Hurley
Hurley.
你就...
Just...
你就... 坐下来
Just... sit down.
我想跟你谈谈
I wanna talk to you.
别重蹈你在商店的覆辙
Come on. don't do what you did in the store.
好吗?
Okay?
没必要... 没必要抓狂
There's no need to... freak out.
没必要抓狂?
No need to freak out?
我当时只是去买些牛肉干和一杯果汁
I'm trying to buy some jerky and a slushee,
突然间你就出现在那蛋糕旁边
And suddenly you're standing there over by the ho hos.
你死了  你想让我做什么呢?
You're dead. what do you expect me to do?
我们能...坐下吗?
Can we just... sit down?
我可能在精神病院  但我知道你死了
I may be in a mental hospital, but I know you're dead,
而且我不会跟你在想象中谈话
And I'm not having an imaginary conversation with you.
我是死了
I am dead.
但我也在这儿
But I'm also here.
好吧  证明一下
Okay, prove it.
好的  好的
Okay. okay.
你当时知道游过去自己就会死吗?
Did you know you were going to die when you swam out there?
为什么不早告诉我?
Why didn't you tell me?
因为你肯定会拦住我
Because you would have tried to stop me.
我想自己既然已经下定决心
And since I was gonna do it anyway,
还不如就瞒着你算了
I thought I would spare you all the drama.
现在你该做些事了
And now you have to do something.
但你在逃避
But you're hiding from it.
这才是为什么你在商店里看到我
That's the real reason you ran
会跑掉的原因
When you saw me in the store.
你知道我是来告诉你...
You knew I was here to tell you--
不  我不听
No, I'm not listening to this.
不听,因为你根本不在这里
No, cause you're not here.
我在这,你怎么跟小孩子似的
I am here. you're being a baby.
等我闭上眼睛数五下
I'm gonna close my eyes and count to five,
-然后我睁开眼你肯定就不见了  -我在这呢
And when I open 'em, you'll be gone. I am here.
-1...  -别闹了
One... don't do this.
-2...  -他们需要你
Two... they need you.
-3...  他们需要你  Hugo
Three... they need you, Hugo.
-4...  -你知道他们需要你
Four! you know they need you.
5!
Five!
发生...  发生什么事了?
What... what happened?
他...  他是怎么...
I mean, how-- how did he...
他是为了帮我们
He was trying to help us.
Jack
Jack.
你不会朝我开枪的  Jack
You're not gonna shoot me, Jack...
只有我才...
Any more than I was gonna shoot...
没装子弹
It's not loaded.
别管我!
Let's do it!
-你知道他都做了什么  -我知道!
Do you know what he did? yes, I know what he did!
我所做的一切...
All I did...
我所作过的...
All I have ever done...
全是为了我们大家好
Has been in the best interest of all of us.
你疯了吗?
Are you insane?!
我知道...说来话长
I know i... I have a lot of explaining to do.
但我从来没做过对不起你们的事
But I never did anything to hurt any of you.
我甚至豁出性命通知你们有个叛徒混进来了
I even risked my life to tell you that there was a traitor in your midst.
-她帮了我们  John
she helped us, John.
你所做的一切都是为了不让我们离开这个岛
All you ever did was blow up every chance we had Of getting off this island.
你杀了Naomi!
You killed Naomi!
确切的说  还没杀死她
Well, technically, he didn't kill her yet.
不  她已经死了
Yes, he did.
刚死的
She just died.
她没有说出来  John
She didn't give you up, John.
她都是为了我们
She covered for us,
还修好了这个  他们在路上了
And she fixed this. they're on their way.
她不是为任何人好
She didn't cover for anyone.
她是想让她的人来这里
She wants her people to come here.
相信我,他们来的时候我们最好已经离开了
And trust me, when they do, we had better be far away from here.
我要去营地那里
I'm going to the barracks.
那里已经被"其他人"遗弃了
The others abandoned them.
那是现在岛上唯一安全的地方
It's the only place on the island with any form
在我想出更好的办法之前我们得去那里
Of security right now. it'll have to do until I can think of something else.
要是你们想活命的话  跟我来吧
Until then, if you want to live, you need to come with me.
没人会跟你走的  John
No one's going anywhere with you, John,
-因为他们不是疯子  -他才不是疯子
Because they're not crazy. he's not crazy.
Charlie呢?
What about Charlie?
Charlie游到那个地方是为了救我们
Charlie went down to that place so we could all be rescued.
而他在那里做的...
And whatever he did down there...
也成功了
It worked.
但一定是发生了什么
But then something must've happened.
最后时刻他一定听到什么...
He must have heard something before he...
我不知道为什么
I don't know why,
但那改变了他的想法
But it changed his mind.
因为他所作的最后一件事就是警告我们
Because the last thing he did was to warn us
船上的人不是我们所想象的那样
That the people on that boat are not who they said they were.
所以我不会听你的
So I'm not listening to you.
我听我朋友的
I'm listening to my friend.
我听Charlie的
I'm listening to Charlie.
还有谁?
Anyone else?
快没时间了
There isn't much time.
Jack  你允许的话  我想跟John走
Jack, with your permission, I'd like to go with John.
去吧
He's all yours.
你说过我们离开不了这个岛了
You said we'd never leave the island.
如果...
If you, uh,
你想跟Locke走  我跟着你
You wanna go with Locke, I'll be right behind ya.
我不会跟那个家伙走的
I'm not going anywhere with that man.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
干我一直在干的事  Kate...
Same thing I've always done, Kate...
活下去
Survivin'.
如果你改主意了,你知道在哪找我们
You know where to find us when you change your mind.
灌篮高手啊!
You ever miss?
Jack
Jack.
是  我结束了个会诊的活儿...
Yeah. I was, uh, on my way back from a consult.
想顺道过来拜访你一下
Thought I'd drop by and pay you a visit.
咱们赌马?(投篮游戏  谁输按horse得字母)
Horse?
放马过来吧
You're on.
会诊咯?
So... consult, huh?
那是否意味你回来做外科?
Does that mean you're back doing surgical stuff?
是
Yeah.
“得了h”（输第一分）
"h."
没有狗仔队缠着你了?
Reporters leaving you alone?
虽然在我出去喝咖啡的时候还有些粉丝要签名
still have to sign some autographs when I go out for coffee,
不过...考虑把胡子留起来
but...Thinking about growing a beard.
你留胡子会看起来很古怪的  伙计
You'd look weird with a beard, dude.
已经h-o了（输两分）
That's h-o.
因此…
So...
你到底为什么要来  Jack?
What are you really doing here, Jack?
我只是来看看你
I was just checking on you,
看一切是否还好
Seeing if everything was okay.
你是来看我是否会发疯
You're checking to see if I went nuts,
是否我会把真相捅出去
If I was gonna tell.
你会吗?
Are you?
该你投篮了
You're up.
算你赢好了  我...
Nah, you win. i, uh...
我得走了
I gotta run.
非常高兴见到你  Hurley
It was great seeing you, Hurley.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉我跟Locke一起走了
I'm sorry I went with Locke.
我应该和你呆在一起
I should've stayed with you.
往事已矣  伙计
It's water under the bridge, man.
我不认为我们做的对  Jack
I don't think we did the right thing, Jack.
-我认为它要我们回去  -Hurley...
I think it wants us to come back. Hurley...
-该尽一切努力...  -我们绝不回去
And it's gonna do everything it can-- we're never going back.
永远不要说"绝对"  伙计
Never say never, dude.
你在想Charlie?
Are you thinking of Charlie?
我们一起逃亡那刻感觉就象一百年前的事了
Feels like a hundred years ago that we came out here together.
怎么会发生这事?
How did this happen?
雷声越来越大了
Thunder's getting louder.
那不是雷声
That's not thunder.
快点
Come on.
你是Jack吗?
Are you Jack?